Every time the rain no longer
falls and I see the sky?
I think back to when I was a child.
Who could only cry?
Blindly chasing after him.
I fell far behind my only thought.
One day I will be stronger!
Bridery and gratitude.
Fading with the wind.
Am I stronger now than I was before?
Or as weak as back then?
I don't know for sure.
But until I do, my voyage will not end.
No matter what's next, I'm
walking straight ahead!
So let's go, there's nothing
that can stop us now!
Though time's all on our side,
we'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall, but we'll
always keep on standing.
There's no way anything will take
what I hold dear away from me.
The voices inside me push
me to keep surviving.
I'll go on, I'll get through,
no matter what I gotta do.
The fiercest of the ball can pour upon me.
I don't care why in the
world would I turn back.
So let's go!
There's nothing that can stop us now!
Though time's not on our side.
We'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall.
But we'll always keep on standing.
There's no way anything will take
What I hope dear away from me?
I know the future's there for us to see.
It's a Tsunami!
Now that is power!
He's straight out of hell!
My sage!
Aokiji.
Hmm, you little squirt.
He froze it!
Artisan!
The whole bay is iced over.
The ship's locked in.
We can't even move.
All cannons open fire!
Save the moving dick.
Well let's move.
We got something to stand on now.
Let's show them what we can do.
Gentlemen we've got
the commander's backing
us up to open fire and
give them everything. If
I'm
not
mistaken
that's the fifth
division commander flower sword vista?
Keep on your toes, Tashigi.
The commanders aren't the only
ones we've got to worry about here.
Every one of these SOBs is a
mighty soldier in his own right.
Yes, yes, thank you, sir.
This ice in the water ain't half bad.
Nice of him to set up some
stationary targets for us.
Let's finish these ships off.
So we can invade the island!
Yeah, I'm not sure it's
gonna be that easy.
They're sending out the
Vice-Admirals of Navy HQ.
It's a rare sight to see them
all lined up in a row like that.
Ain't that cute?
It's like they rolled out
a Buster Call to Greedus.
Too bad.
Because this time we're
the ones doing the busting,
as they're all about to find out.
Hey, Tsuru, why don't you stand back some?
Yeah, please, just leave this
nonsense up to us. Besides,
there's no place safe now, even if I
swam all the way to the end of the sea.
We're setting anchor
here on the ice, boys.
It's time to trounce those Navy sissies.
Now push for solid ground. Go!
We're happy to give our lives for Pops.
It'd be an honor.
Bring it on, Navy.
My men got nothing to fear.
Enough talks. Let's go!
Scored Pirates! Yeah!
Now, it all begins.
You're gonna grace them
with your sword for once.
Ah, run away!
Pumps, noooo! No!
Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
That's insane!
He blocked the world's greatest swordsman
third division commander diamond Geoise.
If we want to stop this
party before they wreck
the place we simply need
to remove the head of this?
This unruly behemoth.
It's Kizaru!
Yasakani's sacred jewel.
It's too bright.
Could you tone it down a little, pal?
He just stopped the admiral's
attack but how i don't know.
It's almost like he's got wings.
Huh we'll fancy that.
The king's off limits.
If you want to reach him
you gotta go through me first.
Scary these whitebeards play
rough what the he's on fire.
He took kizaru's attack hat on and he's
just floating there i
don't know what kind of
devil print that is but
i don't like it even
more rare than logia
powers zoventyte mythical.
creatures. Look!
His wounds are healing!
This can't be real.
That didn't hurt him at all?
Oh, it did.
Don't lie to protect my pride.
So that must be the
first division commander
if his flames can't turn
away an attack then.
They can heal him when it's
done Marco the Phoenix.
Look at that lovely bird
it must be quite rare.
Well that's quite the painful kick.
Now you're lying.
Kizaru!
Hey, giant unit, keep an
eye on the sky from now on.
Oh, crap, here come the giants.
Everyone knock them down.
Attack their feet.
Out of the way.
Clear a path.
Geoise.
Is he breaking the ice?
What the hell is he doing?
I'm dry blocking this one!
It's gonna crush us!
We can't outrun it!
Damn those two.
Cocky hotheads.
What were they thinking
abandoning their post like that?
What if I had done the same, huh?
There'd be no one here to do their job.
RADIRUPTURE!
He didn't just crush that block of ice.
He evaporated it!
Right into thin air!
VOLCANIC RUN!
There's too many of them!
Goddammit!
The ship has been hit!
Everyone, back away!
I feel like we're watching
the apocalypse unfold here.
Sure like to be flashy, don't they?
Hmm, think I'll have you light the candles
for my next birthday, you magma punk.
I'd rather provide the
lighting for your funeral.
How about it old man?
Don't fall back!
Now fire!
PUSH ON!
There!
Get to the plaza!
Take out the commanders at all costs!
Don't let him get ashore!
Seek the Moby Dick!
Push forward and aim for Whitebeard!
My knees are frozen!
I can't move!
It's pointless.
These guys would slaughter
us without a second glance!
I mean, you realize that, right?
Just look around you.
They're monsters, vultures.
There's not a single thing amateurs
like us can do against guys like that.
We've got to run if we want to live, okay?
Okay?
Look, don't be an idiot.
There is no but, do you understand me?
The only thing we can
contribute to this battle is
more blood for those killers
to spill over the ice.
Just listen.
You want to become an admiral, don't you?
There's too much left for us to do.
We're the chosen ones, but Luffy.
I made a promise to him didn't I
What now where is it?
Here he comes.
Attack!
Kill it!
Alright, break down
their artillery defense!
Oh,
my
friends!
Brothers!
Nicely done!
Get up, Little Oars Junior!
He must be related to
the continent, Polar.
He's enormous.
At least twice as big as
one of the regular giants.
We can't let him invade
the island, no matter what.
He'll give them too much
leverage in the fight.
Seriously?
Just look at that beautiful beast.
And I didn't even know that
Oars had a living descendant.
I want it.
I call his corpse after the battle.
Well, that's more like it